A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Washington, DC, Series O FA350
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Presidential Mission to Latin America, May-July 1969; 8; 42.6 Cubic Feet
  - Paraguay - Agriculture (Box 183, Folder 1519)
  - Paraguay - Economy (Box 184, Folder 1520)
  - Paraguay - Book, June 1969 (Box 184, Folder 1521)
  - Paraguay - Economic and Social (Box 184, Folder 1522)
  - Paraguay - Labor (Box 184, Folder 1523)
  - Paraguay - Political (Box 184, Folder 1524)
  - Paraguay - Trade (Box 184, Folder 1525)
  - Paraguay - United States Relations (Box 184, Folder 1526)
  - Ecuador - Finance (Box 184, Folder 1527)
  - Ecuador - Labor (Box 184, Folder 1528)
  - Ecuador - Political (Box 184, Folder 1529)
  - Guyana - Economy (Box 184, Folder 1530)
  - Guyana - Economic Assistance (Box 184, Folder 1531)
  - Guyana - Education (Box 184, Folder 1532)
  - Guyana - General (Box 184, Folder 1533)
  - Guyana - Government (Box 184, Folder 1534)
  - Guyana - Labor (Box 184, Folder 1535)
  - Guyana - Summary (Box 184, Folder 1536)
  - Guyana - Trade (Box 184, Folder 1537)
  - Paraguay (Box 184, Folder 1538)
  - Peru - Fishmeal Industry (Box 184, Folder 1539)
  - Peru - Newspaper Clippings (Box 184, Folder 1540)
  - Peru - Agriculture (Box 184, Folder 1541)
  - Peru - Economy (Box 184, Folder 1542)
  - Peru - Economic Assistance (Box 185, Folder 1543)
  - Peru - Labor (Box 185, Folder 1544)
  - Peru - Political (Box 185, Folder 1545)
  - Peru - Statistics (Box 185, Folder 1546)
  - Peru - Trade (Box 185, Folder 1547)
  - Ecuador - Historical Background (Box 185, Folder 1548)
  - Ecuador - Agriculture (Box 185, Folder 1549)
  - Ecuador - Defense (Box 185, Folder 1550)
  - Ecuador - Economic Assistance (1) (Box 185, Folder 1551)
  - Ecuador - Economic Assistance (2) (Box 185, Folder 1552)
  - Ecuador - Economic Assistance (3) (Box 185, Folder 1553)
  - Ecuador - Economy (Box 185, Folder 1554)
  - Latin America Follow-up (1) (Box 186, Folder 1555)
  - Latin America Follow-up (2) (Box 186, Folder 1556)
  - Venezuela - AID (Box 186, Folder 1557)
  - Venezuela - Budget (Box 186, Folder 1558)
  - Venezuela - Business Leaders (Box 186, Folder 1559)
  - Venezuela - Caldera Inaugural (Box 186, Folder 1560)
  - Venezuela - Economics (Box 186, Folder 1561)
  - Venezuela - Economic Assistance (Box 186, Folder 1562)
  - Venezuela - Foreign Investment (Box 186, Folder 1563)
  - Venezuela - Foreign Policy (Box 187, Folder 1564)
  - Venezuela - Foreign Relations (Box 187, Folder 1565)
  - Venezuela - Government Policy, Communism (Box 187, Folder 1566)
  - Venezuela - Growth Rate (Box 187, Folder 1567)
  - Venezuela - Investment Incentives (Box 187, Folder 1568)
  - Venezuela - Labor (Box 187, Folder 1569)
  - Venezuela - Martz Papers (Box 187, Folder 1570)
  - Venezuela - Overseas Busniess (Empty Report) (Box 187, Folder 1571)
  - Venezuela - Politics (Box 187, Folder 1572)
  - Venezuela - Social (Box 187, Folder 1573)
  - Venezuela - Trade (Box 187, Folder 1574)
  - Venezuela - United States Investment (Box 187, Folder 1575)
  - Venezuela - United States Peace Corps (Box 187, Folder 1576)
  - Panama - General (Box 187, Folder 1577)
  - Panama (Box 187, Folder 1578)
  - Panama - Agriculture (Box 187, Folder 1579)
  - Panama - Canal (Box 187, Folder 1580)
  - Panama - Economy (Box 187, Folder 1581)
  - Panama - Labor (Box 187, Folder 1582)
  - Panama - Political (Box 187, Folder 1583)
  - Panama - Social (Box 187, Folder 1584)
  - Panama - Trade (Box 187, Folder 1585)
  - Panama - Treaty (Box 188, Folder 1586)
  - Panama - United States Investments (Box 188, Folder 1587)
  - Nicaragua - General (Box 188, Folder 1588)
  - Nicaragua - Agriculture (Box 188, Folder 1589)
  - Nicaragua - Investment Incentives (Box 188, Folder 1590)
  - Nicaragua - Labor (Box 188, Folder 1591)
  - Nicaragua - Trade (Box 188, Folder 1592)
  - Barbados - Development Problems (Box 188, Folder 1593)
  - Barbados - Economic and Social (Box 188, Folder 1594)
  - Barbados - Economic and Social Development (Box 188, Folder 1595)
  - Barbados - General (Box 188, Folder 1596)
  - Dominican Republic - General (Box 188, Folder 1597)
  - Barbados - Labor (Box 189, Folder 1598)
  - Barbados - Trade (Box 189, Folder 1599)
  - Barbados - United States Investment (Box 189, Folder 1600)
  - Dominican Republic - AID (Box 189, Folder 1601)
  - Dominican Republic - Economic Assistance (Box 189, Folder 1602)
  - Dominican Republic - Economic and Social (Box 189, Folder 1603)
  - Dominican Republic - Education (Box 189, Folder 1604)
  - Dominican Republic - Expenditures (Box 189, Folder 1605)
  - Dominican Republic - Financial and Business (Box 189, Folder 1606)
  - Dominican Republic - Investments (Box 189, Folder 1607)
  - Dominican Republic - Labor (Box 189, Folder 1608)
  - Dominican Republic - Political (Box 189, Folder 1609)
  - Dominican Republic, Santo Domingo - Newspaper Clippings (Box 189, Folder 1610)
  - Dominican Republic - Trade (Box 189, Folder 1611)
  - Haiti - Agriculture (Box 189, Folder 1612)
  - Haiti - Communications (Box 189, Folder 1613)
  - Haiti - Economy (Box 189, Folder 1614)
  - Haiti - Education (Box 189, Folder 1615)
  - Haiti - Industry (Box 189, Folder 1616)
  - Haiti - Planning and Development (Box 189, Folder 1617)
  - Organigramme du Groupe Special de Travail de la Centrale Hydro-Electique, Francois Duvalier de Pelegre (Box 189, Folder 1618)
  - Haiti - Public Health (Box 190, Folder 1619)
  - Haiti - Summary (Box 190, Folder 1620)
  - Haiti - Political (Box 190, Folder 1621)
  - Haiti - Economic and Social (Box 190, Folder 1622)
  - Haiti - Economic Assistance (Box 190, Folder 1623)
  - Haiti - Trade (Box 190, Folder 1624)
  - Haiti - Urban Development (Box 190, Folder 1625)
  - Jamaica - Newspaper Clippings (Box 190, Folder 1626)
  - Jamaica - Agriculture (Box 190, Folder 1627)
  - Jamaica - Domestic (Box 190, Folder 1628)
  - Jamaica - Economic (Box 190, Folder 1629)
  - Jamaica - Economic Assistance (Box 190, Folder 1630)
  - Jamaica - Economic and Social (Box 190, Folder 1631)
  - Jamaica - Education (Box 190, Folder 1632)
  - Jamaica - Labor (Box 190, Folder 1633)
  - Jamaica - Trade (Box 190, Folder 1634)
  - Jamaica - USAID (Box 190, Folder 1635)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Economy (Box 190, Folder 1636)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Economic Assistance (Box 190, Folder 1637)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Economic and Social (Box 190, Folder 1638)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Education (Box 190, Folder 1639)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Political (Box 190, Folder 1640)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Social (Box 190, Folder 1641)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Summary (Box 190, Folder 1642)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Trade (Box 190, Folder 1643)
  - Costa Rica - General (Box 190, Folder 1644)
  - Costa Rica - Agriculture (Box 190, Folder 1645)
  - Costa Rica - Economy (Box 190, Folder 1646)
  - Costa Rica - Labor (Box 190, Folder 1647)
  - Costa Rica - Social (Box 190, Folder 1648)
  - El Salvador - Agriculture (Box 190, Folder 1649)
  - El Salvador - Fiscal Incentives (Box 190, Folder 1650)
  - El Salvador and Honduras Conflict (Box 190, Folder 1651)
  - El Salvador - Trade (Box 190, Folder 1652)
  - Guatemala - General (Box 191, Folder 1653)
  - Guatemala - Labor (Box 191, Folder 1654)
  - Guatemala - Political (Box 191, Folder 1655)
  - Guatemala - Trade (Box 191, Folder 1656)
  - Honduras - General (Box 191, Folder 1657)
  - Honduras - Agriculture (Box 191, Folder 1658)
  - Honduras - Agriculture, Sugar (Box 191, Folder 1659)
  - Honduras - Economic (Box 191, Folder 1660)
  - Honduras - Social (Box 191, Folder 1661)
  - Honduras - Trade (Box 191, Folder 1662)
  - Mexico - U.S. Borders, Trade (Box 191, Folder 1663)
  - Mexico - Agriculture (Box 191, Folder 1664)
  - Mexico - Border Cities (Box 191, Folder 1665)
  - Mexico - Economy (Box 191, Folder 1666)
  - Mexico - Colorado River Agreement (Box 192, Folder 1667)
  - Mexico - Cotton Textile Agreement (Box 192, Folder 1668)
  - Mexico - Economic (Box 192, Folder 1669)
  - Mexico - Labor (Box 192, Folder 1670)
  - Mexico - Presidential (Box 192, Folder 1671)
  - Mexico - Social Welfare (Box 192, Folder 1672)
  - Mexico - United States Relations (Box 192, Folder 1673)
  - Latin American Advisors (Box 192, Folder 1674)
  - Latin America - Agriculture (Box 192, Folder 1675)
  - Agriculture - Food Balance (Box 192, Folder 1676)
  - Agriculture - Fred Howard (Box 193, Folder 1677)
  - Latin America - AID Economic Data Book, December 1968 (Box 193, Folder 1678)
  - AID (Box 193, Folder 1679)
  - Latin America - Alliance for Progress (Box 193, Folder 1680)
  - Latin American Ambassadors (Box 193, Folder 1681)
  - Assistance to Latin America (Box 193, Folder 1682)
  - Latin American Balance of Pay (Box 193, Folder 1683)
  - Latin America - (Business) General (Box 193, Folder 1684)
  - CACM - Fiscal Incentives (Box 193, Folder 1685)
  - CACM - United States Trade (Box 193, Folder 1686)
  - Caribbean Balance Pay (Box 193, Folder 1687)
  - Caribbean - Communism (Box 193, Folder 1688)
  - Caribbean - Economy (Box 193, Folder 1689)
  - Caribbean - Economic and Social (Box 193, Folder 1690)
  - Caribbean People (Box 194, Folder 1691)
  - Caribbean Trade (Box 194, Folder 1692)
  - Carifta (Box 194, Folder 1693)
  - CECLA (Box 194, Folder 1694)
  - CECLA - Charters (Box 194, Folder 1695)
  - Central America - Agriculture (Box 194, Folder 1696)
  - Central America - Agriculture and Trade (Box 194, Folder 1697)
  - Central America and Mexico - Economic Predictions (Box 194, Folder 1698)
  - Central America and Mexico - Growth Rates (Box 194, Folder 1699)
  - Central America and Mexico - Population Statistics (Box 194, Folder 1700)
  - Central America and Panama - Labor (Box 194, Folder 1701)
  - Central America - Trade (Box 194, Folder 1702)
  - Chamizal Agreement (Box 194, Folder 1703)
  - Latin America - Communism (Box 194, Folder 1704)
  - Latin American Consultants (Box 194, Folder 1705)
  - Cooperatives in Latin America (Box 194, Folder 1706)
  - Latin America - Council Meetings Reports (Box 194, Folder 1707)
  - Latin America - Council Preparatory Meeting (Box 195, Folder 1708)
  - Latin America - Diseases (Box 195, Folder 1709)
  - Latin America and East Caribbean - Economy (Box 195, Folder 1710)
  - Latin America and East Caribbean - Economic Assistance (Box 195, Folder 1711)
  - Latin America - Economic Assistance (Box 195, Folder 1712)
  - Latin America - Foreign Aid - Lodge Article (Box 195, Folder 1713)
  - Foreign Assistance - Methods of Finance (Box 195, Folder 1714)
  - Foreign Assistance - Types of Loans (Box 195, Folder 1715)
  - Foreign Investments - Latin America General (Box 195, Folder 1716)
  - Foreign Investments - Latin America General (Box 195, Folder 1717)
  - Latin America - Economic - Galo Plaza (Box 196, Folder 1718)
  - Latin America - Economic - Gross National Product (Box 196, Folder 1719)
  - Latin America - Alliance for Power and United States Relations (Box 196, Folder 1720)
  - The Church in Latin America (Box 196, Folder 1721)
  - Latin America - Communism (Box 196, Folder 1722)
  - Latin America - Conference - Newspaper Clippings (Box 196, Folder 1723)
  - Latin America - Defense (Box 196, Folder 1724)
  - Latin America - Economic - Newspaper Clippings (Box 196, Folder 1725)
  - Latin America - General - Newspaper Clippings (Box 196, Folder 1726)
  - Organization of American States (OAS) - General (Box 196, Folder 1727)
  - Organization of American States (OAS) - Editorials (Box 196, Folder 1728)
  - United States-Latin America Relations (Box 196, Folder 1729)
  - Latin America - Trade and Common Market (Box 197, Folder 1730)
  - United States Aid to Latin America (Box 197, Folder 1731)
  - Latin America - Fred Howard's Minutes (Box 197, Folder 1732)
  - Latin America - Fred Howard's Papers (Box 197, Folder 1733)
  - Latin America - IDB (Box 197, Folder 1734)
  - Latin America - Industrial (Box 197, Folder 1735)
  - Latin America - Integration (Box 197, Folder 1736)
  - Inter-American Development - Banks (Box 197, Folder 1737)
  - International Grains Agreement (Box 197, Folder 1738)
  - International Coffee Agreement (Box 197, Folder 1739)
  - Latin America - Investment Incentives (Box 197, Folder 1740)
  - Latin America - Labor (Box 197, Folder 1741)
  - LAFTA (Box 198, Folder 1742)
  - LAFTA - Von Lazar Papers (Box 198, Folder 1743)
  - Latin America - Leading Newspapers (Box 198, Folder 1744)
  - News Coverage of NAR - Latin America Trip (Box 198, Folder 1745)
  - Imported Cooked Beef Prepared for DELTEC International (Box 198, Folder 1746)
  - Meat Quotes (Box 198, Folder 1747)
  - Nanny Maginnes - Memos (Box 198, Folder 1748)
  - Memos to the Governor on Latin America (Box 198, Folder 1749)
  - Latin America - Military Expenditures (Box 198, Folder 1750)
  - NAR - Correspondence (Confidential) (Box 198, Folder 1751)
  - Latin America - NAR Memos (Box 198, Folder 1752)
  - NAR Report on Militarism in Latin America (Box 198, Folder 1753)
  - Memos to NAR (Box 199, Folder 1754)
  - Governor's Notes (Box 199, Folder 1755)
  - Conference of the Eighteen-Nation Committee on Disarmament, 1967 (Box 199, Folder 1756)
  - Act of Bogot - Organization of American States (OAS) (Box 199, Folder 1757)
  - Latin America Paper Prebisch, May 9, 1969 (Box 199, Folder 1758)
  - Latin American Peace Corps (Box 199, Folder 1759)
  - Latin America - Police Forces (Box 199, Folder 1760)
  - Latin America - Political (Box 199, Folder 1761)
  - Latin America - Population (Box 199, Folder 1762)
  - Latin America - Press Comment on the Rockefeller Mission (Box 199, Folder 1763)
  - Latin America - Organization of American States (OAS) (Box 199, Folder 1764)
  - Latin America - Press Conference (Box 200, Folder 1765)
  - Private Investments - Latin America (Box 200, Folder 1766)
  - Latin America - Private Sector (Box 200, Folder 1767)
  - Latin America - Public Opinion Polls (Box 200, Folder 1768)
  - Punta Del Este (Box 200, Folder 1769)
  - Latin America - Rural Formation (Box 200, Folder 1770)
  - Latin America - Statistical Abstract (Box 200, Folder 1771)
  - Latin America - Student (Box 200, Folder 1772)
  - Subcommittee of Foreign Relations - Western Hemisphere Affairs (Box 200, Folder 1773)
  - Latin America - Suffrage (Box 200, Folder 1774)
  - Latin America - Sugar (Box 200, Folder 1775)
  - Latin America - Trade Proposed of Common Market (Box 200, Folder 1776)
  - United States Aid to Latin America (Box 200, Folder 1777)
  - United States - Economic Assistance (Box 201, Folder 1778)
  - United States - Investments - Latin America (Box 201, Folder 1779)
  - United States - Private Investments (Box 201, Folder 1780)
  - United States - Recognition Policy vis--vis Latin America (Box 201, Folder 1781)
  - United States - Trade (Box 201, Folder 1782)
  - United States - Trade Mexico, Argentina, Brazil, Chile, Colombia, Peru, and Caribbean (Box 201, Folder 1783)
  - Latin America Treaty on the Protection of Moveable Property of Historical Value (Box 201, Folder 1784)
  - Uruguay Drafts - To Be Typed (Box 201, Folder 1785)
  - Miscellaneous Corresondence (Box 201, Folder 1786)
  - Latin America - General (Box 201, Folder 1787)
  - 1973 Assessment (Box 201, Folder 1788)
- Special Assistant to the President Declassified Materials, 1954-1956, 1969; 9; 4 Cubic Feet
  During 1954 and 1955, Nelson Rockefeller served as Special Assistant to President Eisenhower, as documented in Subseries 7. This subseries contains pages declassified in 2006 that had been separated previously from the folders of the same titles in Subseries 7.
  NOTE: A single folder in this subseries (S1) originates from Rockefeller's appointment in 1969 to lead President Nixon's Mission to Latin America (Subseries 8). Some related documents in this subseries continue to bear U.S. government security classifications and therefore remain closed.
  Subseries 9 of this series contains documents that were declassified by the U.S. government during a review by government officials at the Archive Center from 2003 to 2006. Any document that remains classified since the review has been removed from its folder and replaced with a separation sheet to note its original and current locations. Therefore, all materials in the open folders are now declassified, whether or not the classification stamps on them indicate otherwise. Almost all of the declassified documents prominently display a federal agency's declassification stamp and date.
  In the printed folder list, researchers may wish to refer to the column labeled, "See Also." It lists the folders within Subseries 7 and 8 of this series that are on the same topic but contain documents that were never classified. (For example, Subseries 9, Folder 6 "Cold War Organization--Rockefeller Plan" correlates to Folder 517 in Subseries 7, which should also be consulted.)
  - NAR Appointments and Resignation, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 61, Folder 510.
  - Progress, Status, and Action Reports, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 61, Folder 511.
  - Planning Coordination Group - Agenda and Meetings, Members and Alternates, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 61, Folder 514.
  - Planning Coordination Group - Establishment, Functions, and History, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 61, Folder 515.
  - Planning Coordination Group - Position Room, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 62, Folder 516.
  - Cold War Organization - Rockefeller Plan, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 62, Folder 517.
  - Cold War Organization - Operations Coordinating Board Establishment and Organization, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 62, Folder 518.
  - Cold War Organization - Establishment of Planning Coordination Group, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 62, Folder 519.
  - Cold War Organization - Sarnoff Plan and American Legion Plan, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 62, Folder 521.
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Final Report, February 18, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 63, Folder 523.
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Assignments and Correspondence, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 63, Folder 524.
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Drafts of Final Report, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 63, Folder 526.
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Psychological Warfare - Drafts, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 63, Folder 527.
  - Office of Non-Military Warfare (ONMW) - Economic Warfare - Drafts and Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 63, Folder 528.
  - Four-Power Conference - Pre-Conference, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 64, Folder 533.
  - Four-Power Conference - Pre-Conference, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 65, Folder 535.
  - Four-Power Conference - Verbatim Records, July 1955 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 66, Folder 537.
  - Four-Power Conference - Foreign Ministers Verbatim Records, July 1955 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 66, Folder 540.
  - Four-Power Conference - Aerial Inspection, Overflight, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 66, Folder 541.
  - Four-Power Conference - Aerial Inspection, Overflight (Exhibit), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 66, Folder 542.
  - Four-Power Conference - Foreign Ministers, State Department Position Papers, October 1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 67, Folder 544.
  - Four-Power Conference - Foreign Ministers, October 1955 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 67, Folder 545.
  - Four-Power Conference - Foreign Ministers, East-West Contacts, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 67, Folder 546.
  - Quantico II - Establishment, Membership, Meetings, and Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 68, Folder 547.
  - Quantico II - Drafts of Source Papers #8-14, September-October 1955 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 69, Folder 551.
  - Quantico II - Drafts of Source Papers #15-21, September-October 1955 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 69, Folder 552.
  - Quantico II - Drafts of Final Report (E-1), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 70, Folder 554.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerabilities - Background Papers, April 1955 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 70, Folder 556.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerabilities - Progress Report and Outline Plan, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 70, Folder 555.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerabilities - Development of Vulnerabilities Paper, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 70, Folder 557.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Minutes of Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 72, Folder 568.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerabilities - Policy Papers, 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 71, Folder 558.
  - Exploitation of Soviet Vulnerabilities - Miscellaneous, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 71, Folder 559.
  - Escapees and Refugees - Defection and Redefection, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 71, Folder 560.
  - Escapees and Refugees - Defection and Redefection, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 71, Folder 561.
  - National Security Council (NSC) - Scientific Satellite Program, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 71, Folder 562.
  - National Security Council (NSC) - Basic Policy Papers, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 71, Folder 563.
  - National Security Council (NSC) - Miscellaneous Papers, NAR Handwritten Notes, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 71, Folder 565.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Status Reports, December 1954-February 1955 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 72, Folder 567.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Status Reports, March-April 1955 (Box 2, Folder 39.1)
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Status Reports, May-June 1955 (Box 2, Folder 39.2)
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Status Reports, July-August 1955 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 73, Folder 570.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Status Reports, September-October 1955 (Box 2, Folder 40.1)
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Status Reports, November 1955-January 1956 (Box 2, Folder 40.2)
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Working Groups, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 73, Folder 569.
  - Operations Coordinating Board - Miscellaneous, 1953, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 73, Folder 571.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - National Security Council (NSC) and Operations Coordinating Board Papers, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 73, Folder 572.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Bilateral Agreements, March 1955 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 73, Folder 573.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Background and Development of 50-50 Program, January 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 73, Folder 574.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Atomic Ship, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 73, Folder 575.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - Soviet Activities and Geneva Conference, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 74, Folder 578.
  - Atomic Energy - Peaceful Uses - General, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 75, Folder 581.
  - Imprisoned Fliers, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 75, Folder 585.
  - Miscellaneous Projects, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 50)